grasp-the-nettle.com 2012-06-05

# Privacy Policy | Internet Marketing Business Strategies

Congratulations to Trameka Peterson, Matt Conlon and D. H. Robinson for renewing your EA status. You have each earned 3 x PSAs so far this month... Well done to Ludwina Van Hyfte for getting 500VP and earning 1 x PSA so far... Well done to Nagy Mihaly on getting to EA. I have added you to my Affiliate Rewards List for July! (Today) * * * * * * * * * * * * * * * Congratulations to Abdul-amid Adekunle, Kisal Gilchrist, Kutlwa Shasha, Prima Dolores Cator and Kathleen Packard for responding to the challenge & getting to EA rank before the end of May. I've added you all to my new Affiliate Rewards Program! (3 days ago) * * * * * * * * * * * * * * * There is still a chance for you to be added to my New Affiliate Rewards list in May! Everybody in the first 6 generations of my downline who gets to EA in May will be added to my list and will receive "1 x PSA per 500 VP" accumulted in June! THERE IS STILL TIME TO QUALIFY IF YOU DO IT NOW! DO IT NOW...!! JUST... DO... IT! (4 days ago)* * * * * * * * * * * * * * * Congratulations to: Job Muhwati, Kutiwa Shasha, Tania Neider, Ahmed Habib, Jacqui Iwu, Shoby B Mathew on getting to EA rank this month. I have added you all to my new Affiliate Rewards Program. You will receive 1 PSA per 500 VP accumulated in June! (4 days ago) * * * * * * * * * * * * * * * Congratulations to Kourkoubis Dimitrios on getting to EA before the end of the month. I have added you to my Affiliate Rewards program and will send you 1 x PSA per 500 VP you accumulate in June. :) (4 days ago) * * * * * * * * * * * * * * * Congratulations to Shoby B Mathew on becoming a Bronze Team Leader. I have added you to my new Affiliate Rewards Program for June... (1 week ago) * * * * * * * * * * * * * * * Congratulations to the 3 newest EAs in my team: Kourkoubis Dimitrios, Usanai Jaijan, Joel Ruiz. I have added you to my New Affiliate Rewards List and will send you 1 x PSA for every 500 VP you accumulate in June. :) (1 week ago) * * * * * * * * * * * * * * * Congratulations to D. H. Robinson on winning 50VP in the Daily Grand! (2 weeks ago)* * * * * * * * * * * * * * * Congratulations to Jireh Sy on getting to EA rank. I have added you to my new "Affiliate Rewards Program" and will send you 1 PSA per 500 VP you accumulate in June. Who's Next? (2 weeks ago) * * * * * * * * * * * * * * * Congratulations to Claudio D. Crooks for winning 50 VP on the Daily Grand for the second day in a row! (3 weeks ago) * * * * * * * * * * * * * * * The Following SFI Executive Affiliates Have Been Added To My NEW Affiliate Rewards List: Ludwina Van Hyfte, Claudio D. Crooks, Vishwanath Pillay, Trameka Peterson, Matt Conlon, D. H. Robinson, Sanjana Menon. Next month you will receive 1 x PSA per 500 VP accumulated in June. WHO'S NEXT? (Hint: I am adding EAs to my list!) (3 weeks ago) * * * * * * * * * * * * * * * Congratulations to Claudio D. Crooks for winning 50VP in the Daily Grand! I was also lucky enough to win 100VP. Nice! (3 weeks ago) * * * * * * * * * * * * * * * My NEW Active PSA Rewards Program is GOOD NEWS for 2 groups of people in my downline: (1) Very active PSAs can now earn MORE THAN 5 PSAs per month according to their activity. (2) Affiliates who cannot maintain EA status but continue to be active will also be rewarded. This will FLUSH OUT THE TYRE KICKERS!!! (3 weeks ago) * * * * * * * * * * * * * * * NEW ACTIVE PSA REWARDS PROGRAM LAUNCHING, JUNE 2012: 1. All EAs in my downline will QUALIFY to get free PSAs the FOLLOWING month. 2. The number of PSAs you get will now DEPEND ON YOUR LEVEL OF ACTIVITY! You will receive "1 x PSA" per 500VP you accumulate the month AFTER becoming an EA (even if you don't renew EA status). (3 weeks ago) * * * * * * * * * * * * * * * Congratulations to Ludwina Van Hyfte on renewing EA status! I'll send you 5 x PSAs in June and contact you about a free Wordpress website to promote your business with... (3 weeks ago) * * * * * * * * * * * * * * * I finished version 1.0 of my new, 47 page ebook, "SFI Affiliate Success Handbook: How To Make Money With The SFI Business Opportunity" (worth $35) & sent a FREE copy to those of you who responded to my email. (If you requested a free ebook and didn't get it, contact me & I'll check my email.) The free offer is now CLOSED! (3 weeks ago) * * * * * * * * * * * * * * * 

### SFI AFFILIATE TEAM-BUILDING ON STEROIDS!

4th June 2012 

  * **I've added 5 team members to my NEW PSA Rewards List for July, so far this month....**
 **
  * **I added 22 team members to my NEW PSA Rewards List for June.**
 **
  * From June 2012, qualifying affiliates will receive 1 PSA per 500VP. 
  * I gave away _101_ affiliates in December 2011. (A Record!)
****

**

#### Click the banner to join my team...

**

**Privacy Policy for http://grasp-the-nettle.com/**

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at hirohurl@gmail.com.

At http://grasp-the-nettle.com/, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by http://grasp-the-nettle.com/ and how it is used.

**Log Files**  
Like many other Web sites, http://grasp-the-nettle.com/ makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
http://grasp-the-nettle.com/ does not use cookies.

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**  
.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on http://grasp-the-nettle.com/.  
.:: Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to http://grasp-the-nettle.com/ and other sites on the Internet.  
.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include ….  
Google Adsense  
Clickbank  
Amazon

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on http://grasp-the-nettle.com/ send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

http://grasp-the-nettle.com/ has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. http://grasp-the-nettle.com/’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

David Hurley

**
